[
  {
    "question": "Earth is the _______ planet from the sun.",
    "options": [
      "third",
      "fourth",
      "fifth"
    ],
    "correct": "third"
  },
  {
    "question": "Earth was formed ____________ billion years ago.",
    "options": [
      "4.52",
      "4.53",
      "4.54"
    ],
    "correct": "4.54"
  },
  {
    "question": "Earth is the only planet that supports ________.",
    "options": [
      "life",
      "atmosphere",
      "helium"
    ],
    "correct": "life"
  },
  {
    "question": "Equitorial diameter of earth is ______.",
    "options": [
      "<5000",
      "<10000",
      "<13000"
    ],
    "correct": "<13000"
  },
  {
    "question": "Number of moons of the planet is ?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3"
    ],
    "correct": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Orbit period of earth is __________.",
    "options": [
      "365",
      "365.24",
      "366"
    ],
    "correct": "365.24"
  },
  {
    "question": "Surface temperature is about _________.",
    "options": [
      "-82 to 58 c",
      "-88 to 58 c",
      "-88 to 54 c"
    ],
    "correct": "-88 to 58 c"
  },
  {
    "question": "The earths rotation is slowing __________ millionseconds per hundred years.",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "15",
      "17"
    ],
    "correct": "17"
  },
  {
    "question": "Earth has a powerful ________ field.",
    "options": [
      "magnetic",
      "electro magnetic",
      "electric"
    ],
    "correct": "magnetic"
  },
  {
    "question": "70% of earths surface is __________.",
    "options": [
      "plants",
      "water",
      "air"
    ],
    "correct": "water"
  },
  {
    "question": "_______ is the earths only natural satellite.",
    "options": [
      "moon",
      "sputnik",
      "molniva"
    ],
    "correct": "moon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Earth is mostly made of __________,_________ and __________-.",
    "options": [
      "iron,carbon and oxygen.",
      "iron, oxygen and silicon",
      "iron, carbon and helium"
    ],
    "correct": "iron, oxygen and silicon"
  },
  {
    "question": "The actual shape of the earth is _________-.",
    "options": [
      "spear",
      "oval",
      "geoid"
    ],
    "correct": "geoid"
  },
  {
    "question": "Earth tilts roughly at ___ degree.",
    "options": [
      "66",
      "64",
      "67"
    ],
    "correct": "66"
  },
  {
    "question": "How much percent of water is fresh on the surface of earth?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "4",
      "3"
    ],
    "correct": "3"
  }
]